A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Speeches, Series 33 FA372
Rockefeller Archive Center
- New York Air National Guard - Syracuse, New York, October 1, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 415)
  Ceremonies inducting Air units into federal service.
- New York Retail Merchants Association - Albany, New York, October 3, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 416)
- County Officers Association of the State of New York - Grossinger, New York, October 3, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 417)
- New York City Chamber of Commerce - New York City, October 4, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 418)
- National Legislative Leaders - Reno, Nevada, October 4, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 419)
- Lester Grange Tribute - New York City, October 8, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 420)
- Friends of Lefkowitz - 1961 Campaign - New York City, October 8, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 421)
- Herkimer County Women's Republican Club - Herkimer, New York, October 9, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 422)
- Women's Tea - Friends for Lefkowitz - New York City, October 11, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 423)
- Columbus Citizens Committee - Columbus Day Dinner - New York City, October 11, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 424)
- Westchester County - 1961 Campaign, October 14, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 425)
- Dartmouth College - Opening of New York Club - New York City, October 16, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 426)
- Richmond County Republican Committee - Staten Island, New York, October 17, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 427)
- Alfred E. Smith Memorial Foundation, Inc. - Annual Dinner - New York City, October 18, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 428)
- New York State Association of Industrial Development Agencies - Glen Falls, New York, October 19, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 429)
  NAR received Distinguished Service Citation.
- Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute - Troy, New York, October 21, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 430)
  Dedication of Science Center and Linear Accelerator.
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - 4th Annual Convention - Buffalo, New York, October 23, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 431)
- Vermont State Republican Committee - Finance Committee - Barre, Vermont, October 23, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 432)
- Republicans for Good Government in New York City - 1961 Campaign - New York City, October 24, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 433)
- Committee on State Planning and Urban-Regional Development [Governor's Conference] - New York City, October 24, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 434)
- Eastern Governors Conference on Railroads - New York City, October 25, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 435)
- New York State Grange - Utica, New York, October 25, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 436)
- Girl Scouts, Region II - Albany, New York, October 25, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 437)
- American Finance Conference - New York City - Cancelled, October 26, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 438)
- Sigma Delta Chi - National Convention - Miami, Florida, October 27, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 439)
- White Plains Republican Committee - Eastchester, New York, October 28, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 440)
  Testimonial dinner for Michaelian.
- Onondaga County Republican Committee - Syracuse, New York, October 30, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 441)
- Grand Council of the Columbia Association in Civil Service - New York City, November 5, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 442)
- Message to Legislature - Extraordinary Session - Albany, New York, November 9, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 443)
- Republican Fund Raising Dinner - Topeka, Kansas, November 25, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 444)
- Maine Republican Committee Dinner - Bath, Maine, November 29, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 445)
- Annual Greater New York Dental Meeting - New York City, December 4, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 446)
- Queens Chamber of Commerce Dinner - Queens, New York, December 5, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 447)
- U.S.O. Dinner - New York City, December 11, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 448)
- Republican Fund Raising Dinner - Charlotte, North Carolina, December 14, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 449)
- New York State Women's Joint Legislative Session - Albany, New York, January 9, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 450)
- New York State Agricultural Society - Annual Dinner - Albany, New York, January 10, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 451)
- Governor's Conference on the Improvement of Occupational Safety - New York City, January 11, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 452)
- Connecticut Republican State Central Committee - Hartford, Connecticut, January 11, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 453)
- Associated Press - Luncheon with Directors - New York City, January 17, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 454)
- Albright-Knox Art Gallery - Buffalo, New York, January 19, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 455)
  Luncheon and dedication of new building.
- International Benjamin Franklin Society, Inc., January 20, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 456)
- General Electric Company - Albany, New York, January 22, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 457)
- Minnesota Republican State Central Committee - St. Paul, Minnesota, January 24, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 458)
- Westchester County Republican Committee - Annual Dinner - New York City, January 25, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 459)
- Court Reorganization Meeting, January 25, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 460)
- State Commission Against Discrimination - Dedication of Harlem Office - New York City, January 28, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 461)
- Independent People's Baptist Church - New York City, January 28, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 462)
  NAR receives "Equal Opportunity Award".
- New York State Society of Newspaper Editors - Albany, New York, January 29, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 463)
- Empire State Chamber of Commerce - Annual Dinner - Albany, New York, January 30, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 464)
- Iowa Republican State Central Committee - Des Moines, Iowa, February 1, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 465)
  "RSVP Dinner", nationwide fund-raising dinner.
- Ernie Davis Day - Elmira, New York, February 3, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 466)
  Dinner in honor of Davis, sponsored by Syracuse Alumni Assoc. of Elmira.
- Women's Voluntary Service Award Dinner - Niagara Falls, New York, February 6, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 467)
- Godkin Lectures - Harvard University, Cambridge, Massachusetts, February 7-9, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 468)
- Godkin Lectures, February 1962 (Box 8, Folder 469)
- Godkin Lecture I - Harvard University, Cambridge, Massachusetts, February 7, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 0470A)
- Godkin Lecture I, February 1962 (Box 9, Folder 0470B)
- Godkin Lecture II: Federalism and National Life - Harvard University, Cambridge, Massachusetts, February 8, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 0470C)
- Godkin Lecture II, February 1962 (Box 9, Folder 470)
- Godkin Lecture III - Harvard University, Cambridge, Massachusetts, February 9, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 0470E)
- Godkin Lecture III, February 1962 (Box 9, Folder 470)
- Godkin Lectures - Press Releases, February 7-9, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 0470G)
- Godkin Lectures - Drafts, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 0470H)
- Godkin Lectures - Drafts, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 0470I)
- Godkin Lectures, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 0470J)
- Godkin Lectures, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 0470K)
- Veterans of Foreign Wars - 16th Annual Dinner - Albany, New York, February 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 0470L)
- Press Club - Syracuse, New York, February 14, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 0470M)
- Association of Towns of the State of New York - Annual Meeting - Buffalo, New York, February 15, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 0470N)
- Lincoln Day Dinner Honoring Senator Earl Bridges - Niagara Falls, New York, February 15, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 471)
- New York State Council on the Arts - Albany, New York, February 17, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 472)
- State Commission Against Discrimination (SCAD) - Brooklyn, New York, February 18, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 473)
  Dedication of Brooklyn office.
- American Legion - 43rd Annual Legislative Dinner - Albany, New York, February 20, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 474)
- Chamber of Commerce - Luncheon - Rome, New York, February 22, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 475)
- Federation of Women's Republican Clubs of New York State - Albany, New York, February 26, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 476)
- League of Women Voters - Legislative Conference - Albany, New York, February 26, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 477)
- Broome County Young Republicans - Binghamton, New York, February 28, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 478)
  Dinner for Billy Hill.
- Luncheon Honoring Lt. Col. John H. Glenn, Jr. and Other Astronauts - New York City, March 1, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 479)
- Civil Service Employees Association - Albany, New York, March 1, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 480)
- New York Young Republican Club - 50th Anniversary Dinner - New York City, March 2, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 481)
  NAR receives War Memorial Award.
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People - Albany, New York, March 6, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 482)
- Association of Broadcasters - Legislative Dinner - Albany, New York, March 6, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 483)
- Maine Republican State Committee - Portland, Maine, March 8, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 484)
- Northeastern Republican State Chairman's Association - New York City, March 9, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 485)
- Inner Circle - New York City, March 10, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 486)
- Associated Industries of New York State - Board of Directors Luncheon - Albany, New York, March 12, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 487)
- Legislative Pilots Association - Albany, New York, March 13, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 488)
- Society of Foreign Consuls - New York City, March 15, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 489)
- United Jewish Appeal - New York City, March 15, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 490)
- Governor's Committee on Employing the Physically Handicapped - Annual Luncheon - New York City, March 16, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 491)
- Legislative Correspondence Association - Albany, New York, March 17, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 492)
- North Atlantic States Association of Highway Officials - New York City, March 21, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 493)
- New York Central Railroad - New York City, March 22, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 494)
  Presentation of new commuter car at Grand Central Terminal.
- Citizens Council on Traffic Safety - Luncheon of Finance and Advisory Committee - New York City, March 23, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 495)
- Free and Accepted Masons - Annual Dedication Breakfast - New York City, April 1, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 496)
- Office of Emergency Planning - New York City, April 2, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 497)
- American Association of Industrial Editors - 24th Annual Convention - New York City, April 4, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 498)
- Dinner for President Joao Goulart of Brazil - New York City, April 5, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 499)
- "Salute to Javits" Dinner - New York City, April 7, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 500)
- Young Israel of Concourse - New York City, April 8, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 501)
  Consecration of Synagogue and Community Center.
- Greek Independence Day - Parade and Reception - New York City, April 8, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 502)
- New York State Department of Commerce - Women's Council Luncheon - New York City, April 10, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 503)
- TV and Radio Press Releases - Teachers Strike in Public Schools - New York City, April 10, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 504)
- Alpha Zeta Fraternity, Cornell Chapter - Ithaca, New York, April 14, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 505)
  Dinner initiating NAR as honorary member.
- Economic Club of Detroit - Detroit, Michigan, April 16, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 506)
- Republican Women's Conference - Washington, DC, April 17, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 507)
- Associated Press - New York City, April 22, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 508)
- "Kick Off" Party for MORE Graduates - New York County Republican Committee and MORE - New York City, April 23, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 509)
- American Association of Advertising Agencies - New York City, April 23, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 510)
- Department of Civil Service - Albany, New York, April 24, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 511)
  Unveiling of mural at Civil Service Bldg., State Campus.
- Union Theological Forum - New York City, April 26, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 512)
- Nassau County Republican Committee - Garden City, New York, April 26, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 513)
- Veterans of Foreign Wars - New York County Council Annual Loyalty Day Parade, April 28, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 514)
- Notre Dame University - New York City, April 28, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 515)
  Universal Notre Dame Night.
- New York City Mission Society - 150th Anniversary Dinner - New York City, April 30, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 516)
- Statewide Conference on Aging - New York City, May 1, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 517)
- Adjutants General Conference - New York City, May 2, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 518)
- Chautaugua County Republican Committee Fund Raising Dinner, May 3, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 519)
- Labor-Management Exhibition - "Rockefeller Day" - Rochester, New York, May 5, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 520)
- Seattle World's Fair - Seattle, Washington, May 10, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 521)
  New York Day at World's Fair.
- Political Union Meeting at University of Washington - Seattle, Washington, May 10, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 522)
- Wyoming State Republican Party Convention - Cheyenne, Wyoming, May 11, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 523)
- Colorado Republican State Committee - Denver, Colorado, May 12, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 524)
- Dutch Treat Club - New York City, May 15, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 525)
- Division of Youth - New York City, May 15, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 526)
  Tour of offices of New York State Youth and Work Program.
- Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association - New York City, May 15, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 527)
- National Rehabilitation Association - New York City, May 16, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 528)
  Governor receives scroll and citation.
- Cortland County Chamber of Commerce - Cortland, New York, May 16, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 529)
- American Association of University Women - Biennial Convention - Rochester, New York, May 17, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 530)
- State University of New York, Geneseo - College of Education - Geneseo, New York, May 17, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 531)
  Dedication of health and physical education building.
- Riverhead Chamber of Commerce - Riverhead, New York, May 18, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 532)
- Long Island Federation of Women's Clubs - Annual Convention - Baldwin, New York, May 18, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 533)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union - New York City, May 19, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 534)
  Dedication of ILGWU housing project - Cooperative Houses.
- Mount Mercy on the Hudson - Dobbs Ferry, New York, May 20, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 535)
  Dedication.
- Mortgage Bankers Association - New York City, May 21, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 536)
- New York State Lions Club - South Fallsburgh, New York, May 21, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 537)
- Police Conference of New York, Inc. - Sackett Lake, New York, May 21, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 538)
- National Association of Attorneys General - New York City, May 22, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 539)
  Dinner in honor of Attorney General Louis J. Lefkowitz.
- Republican Women's Club Dinner - Schenectady, New York, May 23, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 540)
- Association of New York State Young Republican Clubs - 30th Annual Convention - Lake Luzerne, New York, May 25, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 541)
- American Baptist Convention - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 26, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 542)
- Independent Order of Odd Fellows - Ithaca, New York, June 2, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 543)
  Odd Fellows Home for Aged and Orphanage of New York.
- Division of Youth - Ithaca, New York, June 2, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 544)
  Ground breaking for Caroline Center Camp.
- Bronx County Republican Committee - Bronx, New York, June 2, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 545)
- Spellman College - Commencement Ceremonies - Atlanta, Georgia, June 4, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 546)
- Montgomery County Republican Committee - Amsterdam, New York, June 7, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 547)
- Belmont Stakes, June 9, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 548)
  94th running of Belmont Stakes. NAR presents Belmont Cup.
- Mount Morris Park Hospital - New York City, June 9, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 549)
- Westchester Community College - Commencement Ceremonies - Valhalla, New York, June 10, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 550)
- New York State Health Department - Syracuse, New York, June 12, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 551)
  New York State Public Health Conference.
- Albert Einstein College of Medicine - New York City, June 12, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 552)
  Dinner in honor of Joseph E. Periconi.
- New York Republican State Committee - Luncheon - New York City, June 14, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 553)
- New York Republican State Committee - Annual Dinner - New York City, June 14, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 554)
- Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Welch Beach, June 15, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 555)
  Dedication and luncheon.
- Empire State Chamber of Commerce - Board of Directors Luncheon - Saratoga Springs, New York, June 18, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 556)
- Women's Republican Club - Wyoming County, New York, June 18, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 557)
- Firemen's Association of the State of New York - North Tarrytown, New York, June 22, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 558)
  73rd annual convention, Hudson Valley Volunteer Firemen.
- New York Herald Tribune Fresh Air Fund - East Fishkill, New York, June 22, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 559)
  Dedication ceremonies.
- American Legion Boys' State of New York - Hamilton, New York, June 26, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 560)
- Conference of Mayors - Dinner - Buffalo, New York, June 26, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 561)
- Carlino Scholarship Dinner-Dance - Lido Beach, Long Island, New York, June 27, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 562)
- Massachusetts Republican State Committee - Boston, Massachusetts, June 28, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 563)
- Saratoga Springs State Park - Saratoga Springs, New York, June 30, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 564)
  Dedication and official opening of Saratoga Spa.
- 250th Anniversary of Schoharie Valley - Schoharie, New York, June 30, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 565)
- Governors' Conference - Hershey, Pennsylvania, July 1-4, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 566)
- Chautauqua Institute - Chautauqua, New York, July 4, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 567)
- African Methodist Episcopal Church Council of Bishops - New York City, July 5, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 568)
- National Republican Club - Washington, DC, July 6, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 569)
  Reception and dinner, 1962 Candidates Conference, National Republican Congressional Committee.
- National Association of County Officials - Statler, New York, July 9, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 570)
  "County Home Rule Congress."
- Rensselaer County Republican Committee - Averill Park, New York, July 16, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 571)
- Business Development Leaders (Nassau and Suffolk) - Dinner Meeting - Riverhead, Long Island, New York, July 18, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 572)
- Dinner for Jackie Robinson - New York City, July 20, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 573)
  Robinson's election to Baseball Hall of Fame.
- Federation of Republican Women's Clubs of New York State - Massena, New York, August 3, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 574)
- Saratoga Race Track - Saratoga Springs, New York, August 4, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 575)
  NAR presents Whitney Stakes trophy.
- New York State Sheriff's Association - Annual Conference - Schroon Lake, New York, August 7, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 576)
- Chenango County Fair - Norwich, New York, August 8, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 577)
  Firemen's Parade.
- Orange County Fair - Middletown, New York, August 8, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 578)
  Governor's Day.
- Fulton Chamber of Commerce - Fulton, New York, August 9, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 579)
  Businessmen's luncheon.
- Oswego County Fair - Oswego, New York, August 9, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 580)
  Tour Sandy Creek County Fair, 4H Club Day.
- Oswego County - Oswego, New York, August 9, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 581)
  Republican Committee Chicken Barbecue.
- Nuclear Test Concessions, August 10, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 582)
- Tour of Beaches by Helicopter - New York Area, August 19, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 583)
- Rotary Club Luncheon - Poughkeepsie, New York, August 22, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 584)
- Dutchess County Fair - Rhinebeck, New York, August 22, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 585)
- Franklin County Fair - Malone, New York, August 23, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 586)
- Rotary Club Luncheon - Malone, New York, August 23, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 587)
- Groundbreaking Ceremony for State University College Campus - Albany, New York, August 24, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 588)
- Grand Union Parking Lot Rally - Lowville, New York, August 24, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 589)
- Lewis County Republican Committee Dinner - Lowville, New York, August 24, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 590)
- Jefferson and Lewis Counties Republican Committee - Watertown, New York, August 24, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 591)
- Erie County Republican Committee - Crystal Beach, Ontario, Canada, August 25, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 592)
- New York State Council on the Arts - Pocantico Hills, New York, August 26, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 593)
- George Washington Bridge - Dedication of Lower Level - New York City, August 29, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 594)
- Syracuse Chamber of Commerce - Syracuse, New York, August 29, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 595)
  Annual state farm dinner.
- SPICE (State Poultry Industry Coordinated Effort) - Syracuse, New York, August 30, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 596)
- State Fair - Governor's Day - Syracuse, New York, August 30, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 597)
- Wayne County Republican Committee - Williamson, New York, August 30, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 598)
- Miscellaneous, September 1962 (Box 13, Folder 599)
- Columbia County Fair - Chatham, New York, September 3, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 600)
- Sullivan County Republican Committee - Annual Dinner - Kiamesha Lake, New York, September 5, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 601)
- State Police - Graduation Exercises - Albany, New York, September 5, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 602)
- Suffolk County Republican Committee - Patchogue, New York, September 8, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 603)
- Seneca County Republican Committee - Cayuga Lake, New York, September 9, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 604)
- Cayuga County Republican Committee - Owasco Lake, New York, September 9, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 605)
- American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Annual Convention - New York City, September 10, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 606)
- Museum of Primitive Art - Opening of Michael C. Rockefeller Exhibit - New York City, September 10, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 607)
- Legislative Candidates' Meeting - Albany, New York, September 11, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 608)
- Consolidated Diesel Electric Corp. - 1st Anniversary - Schenectady, New York, September 11, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 609)
- County Officers Association - Kiamesha Lake, New York, September 11, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 610)
- Brotherhood-In-Action - Cornerstone Ceremony - New York City, September 12, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 611)
- New York State Civil War Centennial Commission - New York City, September 12, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 612)
  100th Anniversary Emancipation Proclamation.
- Nassau County Council of Republican Recruits - Garden City, New York, September 13, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 613)
  Dinner to honor John W. Wydler.
- National Association of State Labor Relations Agencies - Annual Convention - Garden City, New York, September 13, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 614)
- New York State Republican Convention - Buffalo, New York, September 17, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 615)
- NAR Acceptance Speech - Buffalo, New York, September 19, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 616)
- Essex County Republican Committee - Rally - Elizabethtown, New York, September 21, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 617)
- Franklin County Republican Committee - Rally - Saranac Lake, New York, September 21, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 618)
- Associated Industries of New York State - Annual Banquet - Whiteface, New York, September 21, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 619)
- New York State Civil War Centennial Commission - Washington, DC, September 22, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 620)
  100th Anniversary of the Emancipation Proclamation.
- Richmond County Republican Committee - Staten Island, New York, September 22, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 621)
- San Gennaro Festival - New York City, September 22, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 622)
- Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Opening of Philharmonic Hall - New York City, September 23, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 623)
- Kiwanis International Convention - New York City, September 24, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 624)
- Victory Vanguard - New York City, September 24, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 625)
  T.V. Campaign kick-off, WNEW-TV.